{
    "id": "b10b4c70067e40f0982a86d46c4ec538",
    "title": "Infinitives And Gerunds",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is addicted ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to gambling",
                "to gamble",
                "gambling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c20a7fbe4eb74cdbb19a987d2fec42fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am interested ……………………….. to cook.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in learning",
                "to learn"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5ee15eb7e69c446caa6371eadbe363cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Several top designers assisted …………………..  the park.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to create",
                "in creating"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7eee817fc164a71916a8af804c17f31"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is averse ………………….. cards.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to play",
                "to playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bd6cfe8ee5d4ce5915f46c512b1e1d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I do not believe …………………… children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to pamper",
                "in pampering",
                "to pampering"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3d16172389a84228b899a4c5cc8a5ae3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is bent ……………………… trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on creating",
                "to create"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "27c4d79911764278979774dd23dbd1b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have hardly any chance ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to succeed",
                "of succeeding"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5a46a4cbec024e4ab0b342c5a60381ad"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is confident ……………………. the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to win",
                "of winning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "663f78d2b0d24e538d0135858139e7e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is desirous ………………………. his grandparents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to meet",
                "of meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db068d97b0aa4369861d5c25d9b1b0da"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hereafter he is disqualified ……………………. any government post",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to hold",
                "for holding"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb573f589444490797cfe801d65823ba"
        }
    ]
}